pillpack.com 2019-04-12

# Privacy Policy - PillPack

## Overview

Your access to, and use of, the PillPack™ Online Experience, which includes this web site (www.pillpack.com) and the information, community and services that we provide to you and other users through this web site is subject to the PillPack™ Online Experience Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.

PillPack LLC (“PillPack”) has created this Privacy Policy to explain what information we gather from you when you visit our Online Experience, how we may use this information, the security approaches we use to protect your information, and how you can access and correct certain information that we may collect. We’ve tried to keep it simple. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected via this Online Experience – it does not apply to information you disclose to PillPack through offline correspondence or personal contacts with PillPack’s representatives. This Privacy Policy is incorporated and made part of PillPack™ Online Experience Terms of Use.

* * *

## Your Acceptance of This Privacy Policy and Changes to It

By using this Online Experience, you consent to the collection and use of your information by PillPack in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Online Experience. PillPack reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice. Changes take effect on the date that appears on the revised Policy. If you use this Online Experience following a change in the Policy, your use will be understood to signal that you accept the changes. We urge you to review this Privacy Policy frequently for changes.

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on the Online Experience, place an order, respond to communication such as e-mail, or participate in another Online Experience feature.

When ordering, registering or subscribing to any newsletters or other publications, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit portions of our Online Experience without providing such information.

We use IP addresses and session identifiers to analyze trends, to administer the Online Experience, to track user activities, to infer user interests, and to otherwise induce, deduce, and gather information about individual users and market segments.

Like many web sites, we use “cookies” to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our Online Experience. Please refer to the “Do we use ‘cookies’?” section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

When signing up for pharmacy services or ordering prescription drugs, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal and/or health-related information. This information is subject to our Notice of Privacy Practices that more specifically describes how we may use or disclose your protected health information.

How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the Online Experience, or use certain other Online Experience features in the following ways:

To personalize your Online Experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

To quickly process your transactions.

To verify and validate your identity.

To administer a promotion, survey or other Online Experience feature.

To troubleshoot problems with the Online Experience, or any services, as requested.

To enforce our PillPack™ Online Experience Terms of Use, and to detect and protect against error, fraud and other unauthorized or illegal activities.

To attempt to contact you regarding product safety or recall issues.

To provide any legitimate business service or product.

You understand that if you’re visiting this Online Experience from a country outside the United States, you will be transferring personal information about yourself to the United States. You understand that the privacy laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those in your country, and you agree that the transfer of your personal information occurs with your consent. Personal information collected on this Online Experience may be stored and processed in the United States or abroad.

Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?

We can disclose your personal and other information to third parties, as follows:

To vendors whose products or services you have requested, in order to deliver those products or services to you.

To our subsidiaries or affiliates, strategic partners and to third parties we engage to provide services on our behalf, such as web sites hosting, credit card payment processing, order processing, delivery, etc. We prohibit these parties from using your personal information for any other purpose.

To vendors that offer products, services or other information we think might interest you. These third parties may keep and use your personal information whether or not you purchase their products or services. Your personal information will be subject to their privacy policies, so you should contact them directly for information on their policies or to opt-out of promotional communications from them.

In the event of the sale or transfer of PillPack, of one or more of our business units or of some or all of our assets, or in the context of some other business acquisition transaction. In response to a subpoena or court order, or a request from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights, or to defend against claims; or to protect the safety or security of the public or of users of this Online Experience. For example,

We may forward your prescription information to your insurance plan, so that we may handle reimbursement of your prescription purchase for your convenience.

We can disclose aggregate information about users of the Online Experience to our service providers, partners, advertisers or others, but such information will not include personal information.

Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information

You can correct or update your personally identifiable information by re-registering or by contacting us by electronic-mail [hello@pillpack.com](mailto:hello@pillpack.com) or by telephone 1-855-745-4525. It may take us up to 30 days to process your request.

Do we use “cookies”?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Cookies help us in many ways to make your use of the Online Experience more enjoyable and meaningful, such as understanding usage patterns and improving functionality of the Online Experience. For instance, we use cookies to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current Online Experience activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about Online Experience traffic and Online Experience interaction so that we can offer better Online Experience experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our Online Experience visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Mozilla Firefox or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your Online Experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

Safeguarding Your Personal InformationPrivacy and Third Party Links

PillPack follows generally accepted industry security standards to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use such personal information. However, no commercial method of information transfer over the Internet or electronic data storage is known to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of that information during its transmission or its storage in our systems. Other than the these security measures, you transmit data, including personal information, to us at your own risk.

Privacy and Third Party Links

This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by our Online Experience, www.mypillpack.com. In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our Online Experience. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Online Experience and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

Online Policy Only

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Online Experience and not to information collected offline.

Children’s Privacy

This Online Experience is intended for adults. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of thirteen.

Retention of Your Personal Information

We will store the personal information you provide for as long as we believe is necessary or appropriate (i) to carry out the purpose(s) for which we collected it, or (ii) to comply with applicable laws, contracts, or other rules or regulations. Questions and Feedback

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about this Online Experience. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to this Online Experience to [hello@pillpack.com](mailto:hello@pillpack.com).

Your California Privacy Rights

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g. requests made in 2013 will receive information regarding 2012 sharing activities).

To obtain this information from PillPack please send an email message to [hello@pillpack.com](mailto:hello@pillpack.com) with “Request for California Privacy Information” on the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you at your e-mail address in response. Not all information sharing is covered by the “Shine the Light” requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

The information contained in this Privacy Policy is subject to change without notice. Copyright 2013 PillPack LLC All rights reserved.

Effective Date: September 11, 2018
